

Objective

Product designer, with three years of experience in a profound global company, is looking for a position where I can apply my design thinking, project management, and problem-solving skills to make complex problems into simple solutions.



Core Competency

Softwares

Adobe Creative Suite

InVision Sketch

Design Strategy

Concept Development User Research

Data Visualization

User Testing

UX Mapping

Wireframing

Web Development

HTML

CSS

Web Accessibility

Responsive Web Design



Education

Web Development Boot Camp | 2018

- Occupante Codestates, Seoul, S.Korea
- Trained in modern HTML/CSS with ability to build a responsive web.
- In process of expanding the knowledge in JavaScript.

BDes. Industrial Design | 2011-2014

- OCAD University, Toronto, Canada
- Trained with extensive design thinking and eyes to aesthetic.
- Graduated with an innovative yet critical point of view.



Experience

Web Designer | 2018 - Present

♀ Freelance

Providing web solutions for clients in a broad range of industries with sharp eyes to web design principles, information architecture and custom coding.

Key Responsibilities ·-----

Web Development

• Design and develop user-friendly websites. Maintain created design principles in consistency throughout the project.

Client Experience

- Able to listen to the client's company principles and apply it into design.
- Complete the project in time with clear communication.

Product Development & Sourcing Specialist, R&D | 2015 - 2018

P Hansae - Fashion Worldwide, Seoul, Korea

Hansae is a profound fashion vendor that accommodate global partners including Gap Inc., Target, Walmart, and Kohl's. At Hansae I was responsible for product development, visual communication, managing external relations and project timeline.

Highlighted Project: PLM System Design

Re-designed the company's PLM(Product Lifecycle Management) system in collaboration with the in-house software developers. Invited as a UX designer responsible for conducting user research with the department workers, analyzing the existing system's flaws and designing new user interaction to better data maintenance and workflow. The new system dramatically improved work efficiency with reduced work time.

Key Responsibilities

Product Design & Development

- Collaborate throughout the complete product development lifecycle from concept through production.
- Conduct market research according to the client's needs and synthesize the data into a product development opportunity.

Visual Communication

- Articulate visual presentations that simplify complex ideas supported by market research, sales report analysis and trend foresight.
- Meticulously follow client's brand principles to enable visual consistency across the product development.

External Relations

- Daily contact with over a hundred global partners across the industry to develop a product.
- Present design concept and newly developed products to clients.
- Arrange and attend business trips around America, Europe, and Asia for market research and client meetings.

Project Management

- Schedule and attend crossdepartment meetings to coordinate client meeting.
- Juggle around multiple projects at once for various clients.
- Comfortable working in a fast-paced environment with reliable time management skills.